{
    "id": "82a5ec83094f4c708103264321d3d4d0",
    "title": "Comparatives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mount Everest is ……………… than Mount K",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "more high",
                "higher"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8c2f5f634170494bb1fe97ce65b71e96"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sun is ....................... than the moon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more hot",
                "hotter",
                "hottest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "62f52a9e6e78468fabf5713da243cb46"
        },
        {
            "question": "The moon is not as ..................... . as the sun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "hotter",
                "hottest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bae46edd7ee946ed9c56e970d15a7ed7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Iron is …..................... . wood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more heavy than",
                "heavier than",
                "heaviest than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e67d77c4bbdf4280a381ac214b12fbe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wood is not as ......................... as iron.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heavy",
                "heavier",
                "heaviest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42a83a532ce447008fd93b7ed2d14079"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dogs are ........................... than cats.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "faithful",
                "more faithful",
                "most faithful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ee32563eed3746398018f5122ec60cfc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cats are ....................... than dogs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "low faithful",
                "less faithful",
                "lesser faithful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "297f0e0eb48a4e398e0b45a95672020d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sparrow is ....................... than the crow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "small",
                "smaller",
                "smallest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7eab843ebe924aa68988fa1466a08b35"
        },
        {
            "question": "The crow is not as ....................... as the sparrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "small",
                "smaller",
                "smallest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83ab8eca3bf44091a5e139a43ab04140"
        },
        {
            "question": "The elephant is the ...................... of the land animals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bigger",
                "biggest",
                "more big"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "63d38af58c6245918d32becc6d074f7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Samuel is ............................ any other boy in the class",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the smartest",
                "smarter than",
                "the smarter than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d5325e37f61f40749ae2ef9c4b0b3d6d"
        }
    ]
}